[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Green Lantern is a Marvel comics superhero with a power ring which enables him to control the physical world for as long as his willpower allows.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What legendary Hollywood actress starred in Alfred Hitchcocks 1954 suspense movie Rear Window?", "correct_answer": "Grace Kelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Ingrid Bergman", "Ginger Rogers", "Katharine Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tree, which grows mainly in Australia, is the tallest of all flowering evergreen plants.", "correct_answer": "Eucalyptus", "incorrect_answers": ["Acacia cultriformis", "IIIawarra", "Sugar brother"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is used to color the traditional Spanish dish Arroz negro, or paella negra, black?", "correct_answer": "Cephalopod ink", "incorrect_answers": ["Food dye", "Coal powder", "Soy sauce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed \tOskar Schindler in Steven Spielbergs 1993 drama movie Schindlers List?", "correct_answer": "Liam Neeson", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Penn", "Mickey Rourke", "Tom Cruise"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The official motto of this state in the Pacific Northwest of the United States comes from Chinook Jargon.", "correct_answer": "Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Wisconsin", "Pennsylvania", "New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a real place called Cape Fear.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the first full length movie to use color?", "correct_answer": "The World, the Flesh And the Devil", "incorrect_answers": ["A Visit to the Seaside", "The Raven", "The Coward"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The rivers - the Tajo, the Ebro, the Duero, and the Guadiana, are located in this country.", "correct_answer": "Spain", "incorrect_answers": ["Columbia", "Portugal", "Brazil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tiny sovereign state, with a territory of about 0.44 square kilometres, is the smallest country in the world.", "correct_answer": "Vatican City", "incorrect_answers": ["Andorra", "San Marino", "Monaco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character delivered the line, Your mind powers will not work on me boy.?", "correct_answer": "Jabba the Hutt", "incorrect_answers": ["The Emperor", "Bib Fortuna", "Darth Vader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these everyday activities and industrial areas is gold sometimes used?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Embroidery", "Glass industry", "Photography"]}]